export const FLASHCARDS_DATA = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Chlamydia',
      answer: 'A very common STD caused by a bacterial infection. Often doesn’t have symptoms, but easy to treat once it’s diagnosed.',
      options: [
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Genital Warts',
      answer: 'Growths on the genital area and around the anus. Caused by certain types of HPV.',
      options: [
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Gonorrhea',
      answer: 'A common STD caused by a bacterial infection. Often doesn’t have symptoms, but easy to treat once it’s diagnosed.',
      options: [
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Hepatitis B',
      answer: 'A virus that can cause liver disease, which is spread through sex or sharing personal hygiene items like razors or toothbrushes.',
      options: [
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Trichomoniasis',
      answer: '“Trich” is a major cause of vaginitis. It’s very common and easily treated.',
      options: [
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Herpes',
      answer: 'A common STD that infects your mouth and/or genitals. Causes blistery sores. There’s no cure, but symptoms are treatable.',
      options: [
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'HIV & AIDS',
      answer: 'HIV is an infection that breaks down your immune system and can lead to AIDS. There’s no cure, but treatment can help you stay healthy.',
      options: [
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'HPV (Human Papillomavirus)',
      answer: 'A super common STD. HPV is usually harmless and goes away by itself, but some types can lead to cancer.',
      options: [
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Scabies',
      answer: 'Scabies are tiny parasites that cause itching. Passed through skin-to-skin contact, usually during sex. Can be cured.',
      options: [
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Syphilis',
      answer: 'Syphilis is a common bacterial infection. It’s easily cured with medicine, but it can be dangerous if you don’t treat it.',
      options: [
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: 'Public Lice',
      answer: 'AKA “crabs.” Small parasites that attach to the skin and hair near your genitals. Easy to get rid of with treatment you can get at the drugstore.',
      options: [
      ]
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: 'Molluscum Contagiosum',
      answer: 'An infection that causes small bumps on your skin. It goes away by itself and usually isn’t dangerous.',
      options: [
      ]
    }
]